totallywicked-eliquid.com 2015-12-07

# Privacy Policy for Totally Wicked E Cig Store

## Totally Wicked Website \- Privacy Policy

This privacy policy is applicable to this website and not necessarily to other Electronic Cigarette companies websites on the World Wide Web pages. When leaving this Site, please read the privacy policy applicable to the site you are visiting. If you do not agree with this privacy policy, please do not use this Site.

By accessing and using this Site, you hereby agree to the terms of this privacy policy.

**Non-personal information collected automatically –** TWEL USA, Inc. is committed to the protection of the privacy of its web site visitors. Please note that we may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third parties working on our behalf, but these statistics will include no personally identifying information.

**Information We Collect -** in order to respond to your questions, fulfill your requests, or manage interactive customer programs, it may be necessary to ask for personal information such as your name, address, e-mail address and telephone number. We may use this information to respond to your requests, or to contact you via mail, e-mail, or phone to inform you of new products, services, or promotions we may offer.  If you place an order for a product, request a service, or submit content to this site, we may need to contact you for additional information required to process or fulfill your order and/or request. However, unless compelled by applicable legislation, we will not provide this information to a third party without your permission, except as necessary to process your order, fulfil your requests, or manage interactive customer programs. 

You also hereby grant to TWEL USA, Inc. the right to exchange any information provided by you between TWEL USA, Inc.’s affiliates for the purposes mentioned before.

In addition to the personal information that you may provide us, this Site may use technology that lets us collect certain technical information like your Internet protocol address, your computer’s operating system, your browser type, traffic patterns, and the address of any referring web sites.

**Details of what we collect and why below:**

**User name and password -** this is so we can keep your information safe, and so that we can have your information on hand each time you visit us.

**Name and address -** without this we wont know where to send your order or to whom. 

**Age / date of birth –** we operate a strict over 18 only policy on our sites, and we may need to verify that you are eligible to purchase goods from us.   
No information may be submitted to TWEL USA, Inc. by persons under the age of 18.  Persons under the age of 18 may not make purchases or other legal acts on this Site.

**Email address -** we send a confirmation of your orders via email.

**Telephone numbers -** if there are any problems with your order or we need to check anything, we need to be able to contact you.

Payment card number, expiration date, and name of card holder – when you purchase a product or service, we need these details so we can collect payment in the same way as when we take payment in a store. We do not store any card data.

TWEL USA, Inc. will on its own initiative, or at your request, replenish, rectify or erase any incomplete, inaccurate, or out-dated personal data retained by TWEL USA, Inc. in connection with the operation of this Site.

**Correspondence -** if you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.

**IP addresses -** when you visit our site, we will automatically receive your IP address, a unique identifier for your computer or other access device.

You may also provide us with personal information if you contact customer services, if you enter promotions or competitions run by us, or if you get in touch with us in some other way, for example by way of an email facility provided on the website.

Please note that while there are always risks associated with providing personal data, whether in person, by phone or over the Internet, and no system of technology is completely safe, “tamper” or “hacker-proof”, TWEL USA, Inc. has endeavoured to take appropriate measures to prevent and minimize risks of unauthorized access to, improper use and the inaccuracy of your personal information. For example, we use encryption technology when collecting or transferring sensitive data such as credit card information. We do not store any card data.

**How We Use The Information We Collect -** Our main uses of your information are explained above which, in general, is to process your orders as well as to help us understand your needs and provide you with a better service. Your account may be used to store information about your previous purchases and personal preferences. 

But you should also be aware of the following uses:

**Marketing –** we may use the information we collect to inform you, by letter, phone, SMS, or email, about offers and products that we think may be of interest to you. If you do not wish to receive these communications, please let us know. You can also unsubscribe following the instructions that we will include in any communication, such as email, we send to you. We do not share your information with any third party companies or sales companies. Your information is never used outside of TWEL USA, Inc.’s businesses for any purpose.

**Customer care and correspondence -** as part of our customer care procedures, we may follow-up, either by letter, phone, SMS or email, customers who have purchased goods or services from our website or who have posted comments about Totally Wicked on the internet, forum or social media, for example to resolve a complaint or to ask for a testimonial.

**Website improvement -** to help us design our website and improve your experience, we may collect information about the way you use and access our website. Our web system collects information about each visitor, including IP address, the length of time spent on the website and the order in which pages are visited. We may employ third party experts to help us look at this information. However, we make sure that anyone we employ treats all information with the same sensitivity and security that we treat it. This is explained in more detail in the cookies section below.

**Cookies -** from time to time, information may be placed on your computer to allow us to identify you. This information is commonly known as “cookies”. By showing how and when our visitors use this website, this information can help us to continue to improve our website. We will only use cookies to view information on your hard drive that was put there by a cookie from this website. The use of cookies is an industry standard, and many websites use them. Cookies are stored on your computer and not on this website. If you do not wish to receive cookies, or want to be notified of when they are placed, you may set your web browser to do so, if your browser so permits.

**What is a cookie? -** A cookie is a small text file that may be placed on your device when you visit our sites or receive our newsletters. When you next visit our sites the cookie allows us to distinguish you from other users.

Cookies we use and why we use them – without cookies, our sites can’t operate properly. Cookies include, for example, cookies that enable you to log into secure areas. Cookies also allow us to recognize and count the number of visitors to our sites and to see how visitors move around them. This helps us to improve the way our sites work by enabling us to tailor our sites to the way visitors use them. The information we collect from cookies is aggregated which means that we cannot identify you from it.

Our sites also use cookies to provide you with enhanced and personalized features. For example, we use information collected through what are known as “web-analytic” cookies to compare the choices you make to those of our other customers, so that we can learn from those choices. Information collected by cookies cannot track your browsing activity when you leave our websites to browse other websites.

Marketing cookies record your visits to our websites, the pages you have visited, and the links you have followed. We use this information to make our websites and newsletters more relevant to your interests.

Your right to refuse cookies and what happens if you refuse them? - You can refuse cookies by activating the relevant setting on your browser. If you carry on using our websites and do not change your browser settings, we will assume you consent to us using cookies as described above.

**Storage of Data -** we will not store your personal information for any longer than we need to. However, we may be obliged by law to store your communications and personal information including activity logs and we may need to show details of these to government or authorized officials upon request. Like many websites, we use log files to monitor the effectiveness of our online marketing programs.

**Access Rights -** you have a right to access the personal information that is held about you. To obtain a copy of the personal information Totally Wicked holds about you, please contact us via email or postal mail.

**Security –** at Totally Wicked, information security is very important and we have taken many steps to make sure your experience with us is secure. Information about you will be kept safe and secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure of your information, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to protect and secure information that is collected online.

**Keeping your information secure -** to help us keep your information confidential you should:

• Keep your password secret.  
• Never distribute the website addresses for pages that you have looked at while logged in as a registered customer.  
• Password - you should choose a password that is not obvious or known to anyone else. You should never give a third party your password, as you will be responsible for all activity and charges incurred through use of your password whether authorized by you or not.

If you forget your password, you can request a new password, which will be emailed to the address we hold for you. You can change your password anytime through the account facilities on the website. Should we think that there is likely to be, or has been any breach of security, we may request you change your password.

**Payment Card Security -** we use PayPal’s payment gateway to make sure that the details you provide when placing an order are kept private and secure, making shopping on our website safe. PayPal’s secure server encrypts your credit or debit card number details along with your personal information and changes them into bits of code that are then securely sent over the Internet. Your browser will show when you are in a secure environment by displaying either a locked padlock or an image of a key in the grey bar at the bottom of the page; it may also warn you when you are entering a secured environment as you go to place your order. Once we receive your payment information, your payment card is processed through PayPal’s payment gateway. 

**Security in our offices -** access to your information is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information. The servers that store this information are kept in a secure environment.

**Links -** our website may contain links to let you to visit other websites of interest easily, such as YouTube. Once you have used these links to leave our website, you should be aware that we do not have any control over that other website. As such we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information, which you provide while visiting these websites, and this Privacy Policy does not govern them. Totally Wicked is not responsible for any products and/or services featured on any third party website. You should exercise caution and look at the Privacy Policy applicable to the website in question.

**Changes -** we may change this privacy policy, or change, modify or withdraw access to this Site, or the content of these pages at any time with or without notice.

**Contact us.**

**Email: **[info@totallywicked-eliquid.com](mailto:info@totallywicked-eliquid.com)

**Telephone:** Please call during office hours for all general and sales enquiries. 888.761.9425

**Office opening hours are:** Mon to Fri - 9:00am until 6:00pm. Saturday - 10:00am until 1:00pm.

**Postal Address:**  
Totally Wicked E-Liquid USA, Inc.  
2057 60th Place East  
Bradenton, FL 34203
